http://eriksbikeshop.com/privacy

Last Minute Gift IdeasMy ordersCUSTOMER SERVICESTORE LOCATORBikesElectricCycling GearSkiSnowboardSkate + ScooterCLOSEOUTServicesERIK'S Privacy PolicyERIK'S Bike Shop, Inc (ERIK'S) will not sell, share, trade, or give away your personal information. We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience.Collection of InformationInformation You Provide UsWe collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you create an account, post a review, fill out a form or survey, participate in a contest or promotion, make a purchase, communicate with us via third party social media sites, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect about you include your name, password, email address, social media user names and handles, postal address, phone number, gender, photos, product reviews, fit information, payment information (not stored) and any other information you choose to provide.Information We Collect AutomaticallyWhen you access or use our website, or transact business with us, we automatically collect certain information about you, including:Transaction Information: We collect information in connection with each transaction you engage in including product details, purchase price, and other transaction detailsLog Information: We may collect log information in connection with your use of our website, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed and your IP addressLocation Information: We may collect the approximate location of your device based the device's IP addressInformation Collected by Cookies and other Tracking Technologies: We automatically collect information using "cookies" web beacons or pixel tags and other tracking technologies to collect information about you, your interaction with our website and the type of browser and device used. Some of these tracking technologies are deployed by 3rd Party Services to help us better understand your behavior and engagement with our site. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default, but you can change your browser settings to disable cookies. If you disable cookies some of the features of our site may not function properly. We use Google's DoubleClick cookie to collect anonymous 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender and interests). We will only ever use this data to improve our understanding of users of our sites, and the data gathered cannot be matched up to individual users. If you would like to opt out of providing any kind of data through Google's DoubleClick cookie whilst using our site, please visit Google's opt-out browser add-on hereUse of InformationThe information we collect is generally used to:Process your requests or transactionsProvide, maintain and improve our website and associated servicesRespond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer serviceWith your permission, communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards, and events and other news and information we think will be of interest to youMonitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our websitePersonalize our communication with you, including by providing advertisements, content or features we think will be of interest to youWith your permission, enter you into Sweepstakes and Contests run by ERIK'SWe store and process information on computer servers located in the United States.Sharing of InformationWe may share personal information about you outside of ERIK'S as follows or as otherwise described in this Policy:With service providers, vendors, contractors, or agents who complete transactions or perform services on our behalf, such as those that assist us with our business and internal operations like shipping and delivery, rentals, payment processing, fraud prevention, customer service, personalization, marketing, and advertisingWith your consent or at your direction (upon verification that you are the owner of the information)We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.Social Sharing FeaturesERIK'S Website may offer social sharing features or other integrated tools, which let you share actions you take on our site with other media, and vice versa. The use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the third party that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the third parties that provide these features.SecurityWe use reasonable security measures designed to protect information about you from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.Children's PrivacyWe are very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy. Our Website is neither developed for, nor directed at, children under 13 years old. If you believe your child has provided us with personal information, or registered with one of our Services and would like to have this information removed, please email us at help@eriksbikeshop.com with the Subject Line "ERIK'S Child Privacy Request".Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by OthersWe allow third parties to provide analytics services and serve advertisements on our behalf across the web and in mobile applications. These third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to collect information about your use of our website. In some cases, the information in these cookies and other technologies may be linked to other data we collect about you, such as your email address, which we may share in hashed or encrypted form.This information may be used by ERIK'S and these third parties to analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other websites and mobile applications, and better understand your online activity. For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used in this way, please visit www.aboutads.info/choices.We may also work with other websites or platforms (such as Facebook) to serve ads to you as part of a customized campaign. Please refer to the settings of those other websites or platforms for information about any choices they offer in connection with the delivery of interest-based ads.Links from ERIK'S Website to Other WebsitesERIK'S Website may contain links to third-party owned or operated websites. When you access these external websites, the providers of the websites, which may include product or service vendors and other unrelated parties, may have access to certain information about you. Please be aware that once you have left our website, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any websites that we do not control directly and the collection, use and disclosure of information about you by these entities will be subject to the privacy policies applicable at those other websites.Visitors from outside the U.S.ERIK'S is based in the U.S., and if you are visiting the site from outside the U.S., please be aware that information we obtain through our website may be transferred to, processed, stored and used in the U.S. Data protection laws in the U.S. may be different from those of your country of residence. Your use of our website constitutes your consent to the transfer to and from, processing, usage, sharing and storage of your information, including Personal Information, in the U.S. as set forth in this Privacy Policy.Your ChoicesAccount InformationYou may update the online account information you provide to us by logging into your online account. This information should update across the online accounts you use to access our website.For our in-store customers, please send an email help@eriksbikeshop.com with Subject Line "ERIK'S Customer Card Update Request" with the information you would like updated on your account. We will verify that you are the owner of the information and then update your account in our system.Promotional CommunicationsYou may opt out of receiving promotional communications from ERIK'S by following the instructions in those communications or by emailing us at help@eriksbikeshop.comwith the Subject Line "ERIK'S Email Unsubscribe" from the email address you wish to be unsubscribed from promotional messages. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as transactional messages, those about your account or our ongoing business relations.Location InformationThe settings of your Internet browser or mobile device may allow you to stop sharing your location with our website.Your California Privacy RightsConsumers residing in California are afforded certain rights with respect to their personal information under the California Consumer Privacy Act ("CCPA"). If you reside in California, this section applies to you.Subject to certain limitations, the CCPA provides California consumers the right to request to know more details about the categories or specific pieces of personal information we collect, to delete their personal information, to opt out of any "sales" that may be occurring, and to not be discriminated against for exercising these rights.In the last 12 months, we collected the following categories of personal information: identifiers (such as name and contact information), characteristics of protected classifications (such as age and gender), commercial information (such as products purchased), internet or other electronic network activity information (such as browsing behavior), geolocation data, audio, electronic, visual or similar information (such as profile pictures or customer support call information), and inferences we make (such as preferred activities). For more details about the personal information we collect, including the categories of sources, please see the Collection of Information section above. We collect this information for the business and commercial purposes described in the Use of Information section above. We share this information with the categories of third parties described in the Sharing of Information section above.ERIK'S does not "sell" the personal information we collect (and will not sell it in the future without providing a right to opt out). Please note that we do use third-party cookies for our advertising purposes as further described in the Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others section above.If you would like a copy of your specific personal information collected during the prior 12 months or would like your personal information deleted, email help@eriksbikeshop.com with the Subject Line "ERIK'S CCPA Request". We will take additional steps to verify you are the owner of the account before providing any information.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:Mail: ERIK'S Privacy Requests, 9201 Penn Ave S #1, Bloomington, MN 55431Toll-Free Phone: 1-877-885-2453Email: help@eriksbikeshop.com with the Subject Line "ERIK'S Privacy Request".Love gear? Sweet! Join our Email List!SubscribePhone877-885-2453Mon-Fri: 9AM-8PMSat: 10AM-6PMSun: 10AM-6PMTimes are in CSTLive ChatMon-Fri: 9AM-8PMSat: 10AM-6PMSun: 10AM-6PMTimes are in CSTEMAILhelp@eriksbikeshop.comVisit UsStore FinderStoresStore FinderBike RepairSame Day Bike RepairDownhill Ski ServiceSnowboard ServiceKids Ski + Snowboard LeasingProfessional Bike FitShopMy AccountOrdersErik's ExtrasLow Price GuaranteeHalf-back GuaranteeFinancing & LayawayGift CardsHelpContact UsShipping InfoReturns / ExchangesBuy Online / Store Pick-UpWarranty InfoRebate InfoPrivacyDonate Your BikeErik'sCareers / Jr ApprenticeCommunity SupportEvents CalendarDemo WaiverERIK'S Riders ClubERIK'S HistoryPress ReleasesGear ExpertsSizing GuidesBike Buying GuideBike Owners ManualsBike Reassembly InfoSki Buying GuideSnowboard Buying GuideBlogCopyright ERIK'S Bike Shop Inc. 2019Powered by VTEXDeveloped by Driven
